×

Privacy Policy
==============

_Hubbard Broadcasting Inc. Privacy Policy_

_Effective Date: April 25, 2024_

**Any users located within the European Economic Area (“EEA”) are prohibited from using our Website.  For avoidance of doubt, Hubbard Broadcasting Inc. (defined below) is not intended for users located within the EEA.**

This is the Privacy Policy for the websites (“Website”) operated by Hubbard Broadcasting Inc. (collectively, “Hubbard Broadcasting” “our,” “us,” or “we”)(“Hubbard” “our,” “us,” or “we”).  Your privacy is important to us, and we provide this Privacy Policy regarding our collection, use and disclosure practices to help you to make informed decisions regarding use of our Website, and exercising choices regarding our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information on our Website.

This Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference into and is subject to Hubbard Broadcasting’s [Terms of Use](https://hubbardbroadcasting.com/terms-of-use/).

As set forth in our [Terms of Use](https://hubbardbroadcasting.com/terms-of-use/), our Platforms are for a general audience, are not targeted to children, and do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 16 years of age.

**How Do We Collect Personal Information?** 

* **From you.** This includes information you provide when you contact us such as when you call or send us mail.
* **From devices you use when you interact with us online.** This includes information collected through our Website and automatically from devices you use to connect to our Website. For more information about this, please see our “Cookies and similar technologies” section below.

**The Types of Personal Information We May Collect From You**

While using our Website, you may review information, learn how to contact us, watch a video about our company, or take steps to apply for a job.  Depending on how you use our Website, we _may_ collect:

* **Contact Information**, such as your name, home address, work address, email address, telephone number, or other similar identifiers when you contact us.

* **Device information**, such as Information from the device you use when interacting with our Website, including location or IP address.
* **Non-personally identifiable information,** such as the type of browser you are using, the type of operating system you are using, the domain name from which you receive internet access, and aggregate information regarding what pages you access or visit.

**How We Use Your Personal Information**

* To communicate with you, such as when we respond to your inquiries and send you communications.
* To understand how you interact with our Website and your preferences.
* To maintain the safety, security, and integrity of our Website, for example, to monitor, detect, and prevent fraud and improper or illegal activity.
* To debug our systems, to secure our online services, including our network and websites, and to debug our online services.
* To comply with legal requirements and/or to investigate or address claims or disputes relating to your use of the Website. This would include the use of your information to comply with our legal and regulatory obligations, to defend ourselves in litigation and investigations, and to prosecute litigations.
* To conduct internal business purposes, including for data analysis, audits, and enhancing our services.

**How We Disclose Personal Information:**

We may collect, use, retain, disclose, and store personal information collected from or about you with the following entities and for the following purposes:

* **_Service Providers and Advertising Partners_****.** We may provide personal information to vendors, payment processors, contractors, business and service partners, or other third parties, such as advertising partners or other marketing partners who provide services to us, including analysis firms, advertisers, and others.
* **_Government, regulatory, or law enforcement agencies_****.** We reserve the right to disclose your information to respond to valid information requests from government authorities and judicial requests, to investigate potential fraud, or where otherwise required by law. We may disclose your personal information where we believe the disclosure is necessary or appropriate to comply with regulatory or legal requirements, or to protect the safety, rights, or property of ourselves and others and to exercise, establish, or defend our legal rights.
* **_In connection with a merger, acquisition, or business transfer_****.** If we sell all or a part of our company, are part of a merger, consolidation, restructuring, and/or sale of assets or other corporate change, your information may be transferred as part of that transaction.
* **_At your direction._** We may disclose your personal information at your direction or with your consent.
* **_Aggregate Data._** We may disclose your personal information in an aggregated or non-identifying form or otherwise in a form that cannot reasonably be used to identify you.

**Links to Third Party Websites**

We may provide links to websites and other third-party content (e.g., applying for a job) that are not owned or operated by us. The websites and third-party content to which we link may have separate privacy notices or policies. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these websites.

If you provide any personal information through a third-party site, your interaction and your personal information will be collected by and controlled by the privacy policy of that third party site. We recommend that you familiarize yourself with the privacy policies and practices of any such third parties, which are not governed by this Privacy Policy.

**Advertising and Opt-Out Disclosures**

When you use our Services, our third-party advertising partners, social media providers, and analytics providers may collect personal information about your online activity on our Services and on third party websites.

These providers may set web tracking tools (e.g., cookies and web beacons, as discussed further below) to collect information regarding your online activity. In addition, our advertising partners may use this information to deliver advertisements to you when you visit third party websites within their networks. If you would like more information about this practice, and to know your choices with respect to it, please either visit the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out page (currently available at [http://www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/)) or the Network Advertising Initiative’s opt-out page (currently available at [http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)). Please note that you may continue to receive generic ads that are not based on your preferences.

**Information Security**

We use commercially reasonable administrative, technical, personnel, and physical measures designed to safeguard information in its possession against loss, theft, unauthorized use, disclosure, or modification. However, the confidentiality of information transmitted over the Internet cannot be guaranteed. We urge you to exercise caution when transmitting personal information over the internet. We cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will not gain access to your information; therefore, when submitting personal information to us, you do so at your own risk.

**Cookies and Similar Technology**

We and our partners use various tools to collect data when you visit our sites and apps, including cookies, pixels, localStorage, and other similar technologies.  Some of these technologies store data in the browser or on your device. Other technologies may use network-related or other information to recognize your device (e.g., IP address).  Our Services use these technologies, for example, when you first request a web page and data is then stored on your computer or other device so the website or mobile application can access personal information when you make subsequent requests for pages from that Service.  These technologies may also be used to collect and store information about your usage of the Services, such as pages you have visited, other content you viewed, and search history.

We and our partners may also use these technologies to gather personal information about how you view and use our Services and content and to connect your activity with other data we store about you.  We and our partners may collect your personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across different websites when you use the Services.  The use of these technologies helps us serve you better by understanding what you are interested in, tracking trends, measuring the effectiveness of ads, saving your preferences, and storing information you may want to retrieve on a regular basis.  We also allow specific, approved partners to collect data from your browser or device for advertising and measurement purposes using their own similar tools.

Your web browser can be set to allow you to control these technologies, such as whether you will accept cookies, reject cookies, or to notify you each time a cookie is sent to your browser. If your browser is set to reject cookies, websites that are cookie-enabled will not recognize you when you return to the website, and some website functionality may be lost. The Help section of your browser may tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting these technologies, such as cookies. To find out more about cookies, visit [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/). Depending on the make and model of your phone, you may be able to use device settings to opt out of the use of certain device IDs for targeted advertising.

Some browsers permit the user to send a “Do Not Track” (“DNT”) preference to websites that the user visits indicating that the user does not wish to be tracked over time and across websites.  Because there is not yet a common understanding of how to interpret DNT, we do not currently respond to the DNT signal on our websites. We do, however, respond to global privacy preferences when required by law. 

**Updates to the Policy**

We may update this policy from time to time. To the extent permitted by law, any changes to our privacy policy will be posted to the websites and will become effective upon posting. Any changes will be effective only after the effective date of the change and will not affect any dispute arising prior to the effective date of the change.

**Notice Regarding Nielsen Market Research and Measurements**

Our Website may feature Nielsen proprietary measurement software, which will allow you to contribute to market research, such as Nielsen Ratings. To learn more about the information that Nielsen software may collect and your choices with regard to it, see the Nielsen Digital Measurement Privacy Policy at http://www.nielsen.com/digitalprivacy. To opt-out or opt back into Nielson Measurement, [click here](https://priv-policy.imrworldwide.com/priv/browser/cookie-policy-us-en.html?optout=1).

**Contact for More Information**

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or its implementation you may write us at our postal address:

Hubbard Broadcasting, Inc.

3415 University Avenue  
St. Paul, MN 5514  
Attn: Legal

This website is not intended for users located within the European Economic Area.

Copyright © 2024 Hubbard Broadcasting Inc. All Rights Reserved.
